There will always be blood, brilliance and controversy.
QT8: The First Eight is a documentary film directed by Tara Wood.
A detailed account of the life and artistic career of legendary filmmaker Quentin Tarantino, from his early
days as a video club manager to the scandalous fall in disgrace of producer Harvey Weinstein.
A story about how to shoot eight great movies and
become an icon of modern pop culture.
Self (archive footage), played by Quentin Tarantino.
Self, played by Zoë Bell.
Self, played by Louis Black.
Self, played by Bruce Dern.
Self, played by Robert Forster.
Self, played by Jamie Foxx.
QT8: The First Eight is a 2019 American documentary film
co-produced and directed by Tara Wood.
The documentary chronicles the life of filmmaker Quentin Tarantino, from his start at
Video Archives up to the release of Once Upon a Time in Hollywood (2019).
The film features interviews from the frequent collaborators of his films.
The film explores themes of movie business, pop
culture, biography, director, hollywood star.